gethealthyharlem.org 2012-05-24

# Privacy | GetHealthyHarlem.org

**Privacy Policy**  
www.GetHealthyHarlem.org

  1. About GetHealthyHarlem.org
  2. Information collected and used by GetHealthyHarlem.org
  3. Invitations and other communications to non-members 
  4. Use of cookies
  5. Links
  6. Blogs, forums
  7. Correcting/updating or removing information
  8. Email choice/opt-out
  9. Security
  10. Sharing and disclosure of information GetHealthyHarlem.org collects
  11. Changes to our privacy policy
  12. Contacting the website

 **1.   About GetHealthyHarlem.org**  
GetHealthyHarlem.org is an online service that allows our members to set up unique personal profiles and connect with other people in the Harlem community who are interested in health and wellness. GetHealthyHarlem.org members can view each others' profiles, meet and communicate with other members through blogs and forums. The site will allow members to make new friends and contacts or invite people they already know who share their health and wellness interests to join the site. They can also learn from community health experts who blog, contribute articles or are profiled on the site. GetHealthyHarlem.org members can change their profile information at any time and can control how the members and the service communicate with them.

GetHealthyHarlem.org cares deeply about online privacy. If you have any questions concerning this privacy policy, please Contact Us.

Top of page

**2.   Information Collected and Used by GetHealthyHarlem.org**  
GetHealthyHarlem.org collects user submitted information such as name and email address to authenticate users and to send notifications to those users relating to the GetHealthyHarlem.org service. GetHealthyHarlem.org also collects other profile data including but not limited to: personal interests, gender, age, in order to assist users in finding and communicating with one another. GetHealthyHarlem.org does not collect medical information or health records.

GetHealthyHarlem.org also logs non-personally identifiable information including IP address, profile information, aggregate user data, and browser type, from users and visitors to the site. This data is used to manage the website, track usage and improve the website services. User IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes.

User profile information including members' pictures and usernames are displayed to people in order to facilitate user interaction in the GetHealthyHarlem.org social networking community. Email addresses are used for the purposes of inviting new friends to join GetHealthyHarlem.org, to add users to members' friends' networks, and to send notifications related to the service. With the exception of inviting friends, adding friends, and notifications, a user's email address is not shared or displayed to people within the site. Users can communicate with each other through blogs and forums without disclosing their email addresses. Users' full names are never directly revealed to other members. 

We may also use a user's email address to send updates, news regarding the service, health tips or reminders. Users may choose not to receive email of this type by changing their "notification" setting to "Do not send me notification emails" in the user "Account Settings." 

From time to time, GetHealthyHarlem.org, may sponsor a special program or contest on GetHealthyHarlem.org. Users may be asked to provide personal information including name, email address or home address or to answer questions in order to participate. It will be clear at the point of collection who is collecting the personal information and whose privacy statement will apply.

Top of page 

**3.   Invitations and Other Communications to Non-members**  
GetHealthyHarlem.org members can invite friends to join the service by sending invitation emails via our automated invitation system. GetHealthyHarlem.org stores the email addresses that members provide in order to be able to add the friends to members' buddylists and also to send reminders of the invitations. GetHealthyHarlem.org does not sell these email addresses or use them to send any other communication besides invitations and invitation reminders (up to three (3) per email address). Recipients of invitations from GetHealthyHarlem.org may contact GetHealthyHarlem.org at to request the removal of their information from our database.

You may prevent GetHealthyHarlem.org email invitations and other messages from being sent to any email address you control by sending a single email to with the subject "BLOCK." To do so, please Contact Us.

Top of page 

**4.   Use of Cookies**  
GetHealthyHarlem.org uses cookies to store visitor's preferences, to customize newsletter, advertising, and Web page session information. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set-each browser is different, so check the "help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences-however, you must enable cookies from GetHealthyHarlem.org in order to use most functions on the site. 

Top of page

 **5.   Links**  
GetHealthyHarlem.org contains links to sites. GetHealthyHarlem.org is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site a user should read the privacy polity stated on that site. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on GetHealthyHarlem.org.

Top of page

**6.   Blogs, Forums **  
Please be aware that whenever you voluntarily post public information to blogs, forums, resources, calendars or any other public forum, the information posted can be accessed by the public and can in turn be used by those people to send you unsolicited communications.

Top of page

**7.   Correcting/Updating or Removing Information**  
GetHealthyHarlem.org users may modify or remove any of their personal information at any time by logging into their account and accessing features such as Edit Profile and Account Info.

Top of page

**8.   Email Choice/Opt-out**  
Members who no longer wish to receive updates or notifications may choose not to by selecting "Do not send me notification of emails" in the user profile "Account Settings." Users who do not wish to receive myhelathyharlem.net health tips and reminders, newsletters, and web editor's picks may choose not to by selecting "Do not send me GetHealthyHarlem.org tips/reminders/newsletters/editor's picks" in the user profile "Account Settings." All notification emails and GetHealthyHarlem.org tips/reminders/newsletters/editor's picks also include the above instructions for opting-out of those communications in the future.

Top of page

**9.   Security **  
GetHealthyHarlem.org member accounts are secured by member-created passwords. GetHealthyHarlem.org takes precautions to insure that member account information is kept private. We use reasonable measures to protect member information that is stored within our database, and we restrict access to member information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions, such as our customer service personnel and technical staff. Please note that we cannot guarantee the security of member account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of member information at any time. For any additional information about the security measures we use on GetHealthyHarlem.org, please Contact Us.

Top of page

**10.   Sharing and Disclosure of Information GetHealthyHarlem.org collects**  
Except as otherwise described in this privacy statement, GetHealthyHarlem.org will not disclose personal information to any third party unless we believe that disclosure is necessary: 1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpooena, search warrant, or other legal process received by GetHealthyHarlem.org, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; 2) to enforce the GetHealthyHarlem.org Terms of Use Agreement or to protect our rights; or 3) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of the service. GetHealthyHarlem.org reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of GetHealthyHarlem.org or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest. For more information see the "Changes in Our Privacy Policy" section below.

Top of page

**11.   Changes to Our Privacy Policy**  
From time to time we may make changes to our privacy policy. If we make changes, we will post them on our site to make users aware of what the changes are so users will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and when we may disclose it. A user is bound by any minor changes to the policy when he or she uses the site after those changes have been posted. If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify by posting a notice on our Web site for 30 days.

Top of page

**12.   Contacting the Website**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please Contact Us. 

Top of page

Last modified: January 7, 2009
